Guide to the Records of the Institute of African American Affairs RG.9.8
New York University Archives
- Series IV: Audiovisual Recordings
  - Subseries A: The Soul of Reason Audio Recordings
    - Addison, Gayle -- writer, critic and Associate Professor of English at Baruch College of the City University of New York., 1975 November 12; RG9.8-84; Format: Reel TRT: 29:00 (Box 41, Folder 84)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Gayle Addison discuss the status of Black writing.
    - Goodwin, Steven -- Investment Counselor and Option Specialist for U.S. Option International, Inc., 1975 November 12; RG9.8-13; Format: Reel TRT: unknown (Box 40, Folder 13)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Steven Goodwin discuss the status of the stock market in 1975 and the ways in which a decrease in the demand for municipal bonds affected the Black community.
    - Furman, Roger -- playwright and Director of the New Heritage Repertory Theatre in Harlem., 1975 December 10; RG9.8-16; Format: Reel TRT: 28:30 (Box 40, Folder 16)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Roger Furman discuss Furman's new play Fat Tuesday about Black life in New Orleans during the 1930s, as well as other developments in Black theater.
    - Bailey, Peter -- Associate Editor of Black Enterprise Magazine., 1975; RG9.8-10; Format: Reel TRT: 29:35 (Box 40, Folder 10)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Peter Bailey discuss the 1975-1976 dance and theater season, including productions on and off Broadway.
    - Harris, Diane, Frances Gibson, and William Kornblum -- Public Involvement Assistant, Recreation Specialist, and a member of the planning board for the Gateway National Recreation Area., 1975; RG9.8-11; Format: Reel TRT: 28:30 (Box 40, Folder 11)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr., Diane Harris, Frances Gibson, and William Kornblum discuss planning for the Gateway National Recreation Area, a federal public park.
    - Clark, Sam -- radio personality and producer of the record Black Americans., 1976 January 7; RG9.8-17; Format: Reel TRT: 28:30 (Box 40, Folder 17)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Sam Clark discuss Clark's record Black Americans, a record that addresses Blacks and the United States Bicentennial, and whether or not the Black man is still fighting the United States government.
    - Frazier, Cliff -- Administrator of Third World Cinema., 1976 January 7; RG9.8-20; Format: Reel TRT: 28:30 (Box 40, Folder 20)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Cliff Frazier discuss trends in Black filmmaking, including the roles portrayed by Black actors in Black films.
    - Coombs, Orde -- author and critic., 1976 January 13; RG9.8-126; Format: Reel TRT: 29:25 (Box 50, Folder 126)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Orde Coombs speak about Coombs' tour of the People's Republic of China the previous year.
    - Carr, Ivory -- Assistant Director of Ambulatory Care at Brooklyn Jewish Hospital and Medical Center., 1976 January 14; RG 9.8-18; Format: Reel TRT: 28:30 (Box 40, Folder 18)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Ivory Carr discuss child abuse.
    - Bullock, Kathleen, Mark Millander, and Terry Smith -- students from the New York City Executive High School Intern Program., 1976 January 21; RG9.8-196; Format: Reel TRT: 28:50 (Box 54, Folder 196)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and students Kathleen Bullock, Mark Millander, and Terry Smith discuss the professional development opportunities made available by the New York City Executive High School Intern Program.
    - Hutson, Jean Blackwell -- Chief of the Schomburg Center for Research in Black Culture., 1976 February 4; RG9.8-22; Format: Reel TRT: 28:30 (Box 40, Folder 22)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Jean Blackwell Hutson discuss how a grant from the National Endowment for the Humanities allowed the Schomburg Center to gain bibliographic control over its collections. They discuss different aspects of the center's history with the New York Public Library and speak about fundraising efforts for a new, larger structure.
    - Wallace, Robert E. -- Executive Director of the National Interagency Council on Smoking and Health., 1976 February 4; RG9.8-19; Format: Reel TRT: 28:30 (Box 40, Folder 19)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Robert E. Wallace discuss ways to decrease smoking in the United States.
    - Barnes, Arthur -- President of the New York Urban Coalition., 1976 February 18; RG9.8-159; Format: Reel TRT: 28:50 (Box 53, Folder 159)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Arthur Barnes discuss the progress and programs of the New York Urban Coalition, which was founded in the late 1960s in order to address unrest within the Black and Puerto Rican communities.
    - Suggs, Dr. Dolores -- Assistant to the Dean of Student Affairs at the New York University College of Dentistry., 1976 March 3; RG9.8-197; Format: Reel TRT: 28:50 (Box 54, Folder 197)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Dr. Dolores Suggs discuss what is being done to train more Black men and women to address dental problems in the Black community.
    - Armstead-Johnson, Dr. Helen -- Director of the Afro-American Theater Museum and Professor of English at York College of the City University of New York., 1976 March 23; RG9.8-125; Format: Reel TRT: 28:35 (Box 50, Folder 125)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Helen Armstead-Johnson discuss the collection Armstead-Johnson has assembled about the development of Afro-American theatre.
    - White, Dr. Herbert -- representative from the New York City Department of Personnel., 1976 April 28; RG9.8-124; Format: Reel TRT: 28:50 (Box 50, Folder 124)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Dr. Herbert White discuss how recent cutbacks in New York City have had an adverse impact on minority employees.
    - Walker, Dr. Wyatt T. -- Canaan Baptist Church of Harlem., 1976 May 11; RG9.8-73; Format: Reel TRT: 28:50 (Box 41, Folder 73)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Dr. Wyatt T. Walker discuss the role of the Black church, which, historically, was the most pervasive social force within the Black community.
    - Bailey, Peter -- Executive Director of the Black Theatre Alliance., 1976 May 26; RG9.8-169; Format: Reel TRT: 29:00 (Box 55, Folder 169)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Peter Bailey discuss ways the Black Theatre Alliance promotes the work of 36 theatre and dance organizations.
    - Moore, Bob and Jean Carrie Bond -- representatives from The Council on Interracial Books for Children and the Foundation for Change., 1976 June 1; RG9.8-121; Format: Reel TRT: unknown (Box 50, Folder 121)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr., Bob Moore, and Jean Carrie Bond discuss racial stereotypes found in books for children.
    - Patterson, Pat and Fatima Shaik -- Editor-at-Large at Black Enterprise Magazine, and staff member of the Institute of Afro-American Affairs at New York University and Coordinator for the AEJ Summer Journalism Program., 1976 June 29; RG9.8-123; Format: Reel TRT: 29:00 (Box 50, Folder 123)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr., Pat Patterson, and Fatima Shaik discuss opportunities, like the AEJ Summer Journalism Porgram, that allow minority students to explore the field of journalism.
    - Brown, Howard -- Medical Director of The New York Times and Assistant Professor of Clinical Medicine at New York University., 1976 June 30; RG9.8-122; Format: Reel TRT: unknown (Box 50, Folder 122)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Howard Brown discuss ways to increase the number of Black physicians in the United States.
    - Greaves, William -- independent filmmaker and producer of From These Roots., 1976 June 30; RG9.8-181; Format: Reel TRT: 29:00 (Box 55, Folder 181)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and William Greaves discuss how Black filmmakers during the 1960s and 1970s moved to the forefront of independent filmmakers.
    - Patterson, John, Jr. -- President of the South Bronx Economic Development Corporation., 1976 June 30; RG9.8-182; Format: Reel TRT: 29:00 (Box 55, Folder 182)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and John Patterson, Jr. discuss the Bronx businesses aided by the South Bronx Economic Decvelopment Corporation.
    - Morris, Horace -- Executive Director of the New York Urban League., 1976 July 7; RG9.8-198; Format: Reel TRT: 29:30 (Box 54, Folder 198)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Horace Morris discuss the mission of the New York Urban League to serve the minorities of New York.
    - Wein, Joyce -- Associate Producer of Newport in New York Jazz Festival., 1976 July 13; RG9.8-106; Format: Reel TRT: 28:50 (Box 41, Folder 106)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Joyce Wein discuss the legacy of jazz music in America and which musicians will be featured in the upcoming Newport in New York Jazz Festival.
    - Dinkins, David -- Chairman for the Council of Black Elected Democrats of New York State., 1976 August 11; RG9.8-143; Format: Reel TRT: 28:40 (Box 53, Folder 143)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and David Dinkins discuss Black politics and the significance of the Black vote.
    - Webb, Dr. Arnold -- Executive Director of the Division of Educational Planning and Support for the New York City Board of Education., 1976 September 21; RG9.8-164; Format: Reel TRT: 29:30 (Box 53, Folder 164)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Dr. Arnold Webb discuss budget cuts to the New York City Board of Education.
    - Carter, Dr. Ralph D. -- Assistant Professor of History at Livingston College of Rutgers University., 1976 September 26; RG9.8-67; Format: Reel TRT: 29:30 (Box 52, Folder 67)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Dr. Ralph D. Carter discuss the Black community's participation in and perspective on the American Bicentennial.
    - Patterson, Pat -- Editor-At-Large at Black Enterprise magazine and instructor from the Association for Journalism's Summer Institute for Minorities., 1976 October 12; RG9.8-66; Format: Reel TRT: 29:00 (Box 52, Folder 66)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Pat Patterson discuss reasons why only two percent of those employed in the field of journalism are from minority groups.
    - Robeson, Paul, Jr. -- Head of the Paul Robeson Archives., 1976 October 20; RG9.8-179; Format: Reel TRT: 29:00 (Box 55, Folder 179)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Paul Robeson, Jr. discuss fundraising for and the processing of the Paul Robeson Archives, which documents Robeson's life as an actor, singer, and figure of the civil rights movement.
    - Bondurant, Marion, Dr. Beny J. Primm, and Clementine Butts -- Director of Development, Co-Chairperson, and Benefit Committee Chairperson from National Medical Fellowships, Inc., 1976 October 26; RG9.8-65; Format: Reel TRT: 29:00 (Box 52, Folder 65)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr., Clementine Butts, Dr. Beny J. Primm, and Marion Bondurant discuss the fundraising efforts of the National Medical Fellowship, Inc. for Black medical students.
    - Holloman, Dr. J. L. S. -- President of the New York City Health and Hospital Corporation., 1976 October 27; RG9.8-120; Format: Reel TRT: 29:00 (Box 50, Folder 120)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Dr. J. L. S. Holloman discuss the effects of New York City's fiscal crisis on healthcare for Black, Hispanic, and economically-deprived individuals.
    - Florence Jackson, Carol Banks, and Robert Williams -- Director for the Center for the Humanities and the Arts of the New York City Board of Education, staff member of the Institute of Afro-American Affairs at New York University, and the Director of Community Affairs for the New York City Bicentennial Corporation., 1976 November 2; RG9.8-64; Format: Reel TRT: 29:00 (Box 52, Folder 64)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr., Carol Banks, Florence Jackson, and Robert Williams discuss the booklet Ebony Patriots, which describes the participation of Black soldiers in various battles of the Revolutionary War in New York City and its surroundings.
    - Herring, Leonard -- Public Relations Specialist for the film Sounder Part 2., 1976 November 30; RG9.8-119; Format: Reel TRT: 29:00 (Box 50, Folder 119)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Leonard Herring discuss the promotion of Black films, including Sounder Part 2, a film about a Black family in Louisiana.
    - Pigatt, Anderson -- sculptor., 1976 December 7; RG9.8-118; Format: Reel TRT: 29:00 (Box 50, File 118)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Anderson Pigatt discuss the role of the Black artist at a time when the recognition of the Black artist was increasing across the United States and, in New York City, many Black artists were opening their own galleries.
    - Lynch, Dr. Hollis -- Professor of History for the Institute of African Studies at Columbia University., 1976 December 14; RG9.8-117; Format: Reel TRT: 29:00 (Box 50, Folder 117)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Dr. Hollis Lynch discuss how recent problems in South Africa have highlighted the important of Africa in world affairs. They also speak more specifically about Black America's response to South Africa.
    - Gutman, Dr. Herbert -- professor and author of the Black Family in Slavery and Freedom., 1976 December 28; RG9.8-116; Format: Reel TRT: 29:00 (Box 50, Folder 116)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Dr. Herbert Gutman discuss the dynamic of the Black family in the United States, a topic explored in Gutman's book Black Family in Slavery and Freedom.
    - Perkins, William Eric and Eric Foner -- professor from Temple University, and professor from City College of the City University of New York., 1977 January 4; RG9.8-115; Format: Reel TRT: 29:00 (Box 50, Folder 115)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr., William Eric Perkins, and Eric Foner discuss controversial new books about Blacks during slavery, including Charles Wesley's Roll, Jordan, Roll.
    - Basil Patterson -- Vice Chairman of the Democratic National Committee., 1977 January 6; RG9.8-168; Format: Reel TRT: 29:30 (Box 55, Folder 168)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Basil Patterson discuss the effects of the Carter administration on the Black community.
    - Alston, Dr. Lester -- a clinical psychologist and Associate Professor of Education at Baruch College of the City University of New York., 1977 January 12; RG9.8-199; Format: Reel TRT: 29:30 (Box 54, Folder 199)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Dr. Lester Alston discuss mental health issues in the Black community.
    - Sutton, Honorable Percy E. -- Borough President of Manhattan., 1977 January 12; RG9.8-161; Format: Reel TRT: 29:30 (Box 53, Folder 161)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Percy Sutton discuss political opportunities and responsibilities of minorities during the Carter administration. They also discuss Sutton's plans for running for the Mayor of New York City.
    - Deas, Dr. Gerald -- physician from the Department of Internal Medicine at Jamaica Hospital., 1977 January 19; RG9.8-63; Format: Reel TRT: 29:30 (Box 52, Folder 63)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Dr. Gerald Deas discuss the consumption of laundry starch by tens of thousands of Black Americans and how its consumption leads to a higher proportion of iron deficiency anemia in the Black population.
    - Olugebefula, Dr. Ademola and Jean Taylor -- Vice President of the National Board of Directors and Executive Secretary of the National Conference of Artists., 1977 February 9; RG9.8-170; Format: Reel TRT: 29:30 (Box 55, Folder 170)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr., Dr. Ademola Olugebefula, and Jean Taylor discuss the upcoming National Conference of Artists, which involves artists, patrons and educators.
    - Ward, Willie and Howard Scheffey -- President, and past president and Chairman of the Board of the New York City Black Policemen's Organization The Guardians., 1977 February 22; RG9.8-62; Format: Reel TRT: 29:30 (Box 52, Folder 62)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr., Willie Ward, and Howard Scheffey discuss Black policemen in New York City, their affiliation with the Police Benevolent Association (PBA), and the way in which criminal justice and law enforcement is applied within the Black community. Their discussion occurs shortly after The Guardians Association of the Police Department of the City of New York, the Black policeman's organization of New York City, endorsed implementation of a resolution to terminante affiliation with the PBA.
    - French, Arthur -- performer in the Negro Ensemble Company's play Brownsville Raid., 1977 March 1; RG9.8-61; Format: Reel TRT: 29:30 (Box 52, Folder 61)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Arthur French discuss how, on August 13, 1906, 167 Black soldiers of the 25th Infantry Division were dishonorably discharged by Theodore Roosevelt for their participation in the now infamous Brownsville Raid.
    - Burns, Dr. Haywood -- Associate Professor of Law at the New York University School of Law., 1977 March 8; RG9.8-60; Format: Reel TRT: 29:30 (Box 52, Folder 60)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Dr. Haywood Burns discuss the controversial appointment of Griffin Bell to the position of Attorney General of the United States.
    - Rodgers, Rod -- choreographer and Director of the Rod Rodgers Dance Company., 1977 March 14; RG9.8-114; Format: Reel TRT: 29:30 (Box 50, Folder 114)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Rod Rodgers discuss the role of Black dance companies in the artistic life of America.
    - Jackson, Florence -- Director for the Center for the Humanities and Arts for the New York City Board of Education., 1977 March 16; RG9.8-171; Format: Reel TRT: 29:30 (Box 55, Folder 171)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Florence Jackson discuss how the television mini-series Roots has inspired school curriculums.
    - Cooper, Jocelyn and Patricia Dempsey -- Coordinator of Foods and Nutrition of the Council Against Poverty and the Community Development Agency, and the Deputy Director of Food-Stamp Alert., 1977 March 22; RG9.8-59; Format: Reel TRT: 29:30 (Box 52, Folder 59)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr., Jocelyn Cooper, and Patricia Dempsey discuss why over a million Black individuals who are eligible for food stamps are not receiving such benefits.
    - Goldman, Cathy and James Hill -- representatives from the New York City School Breakfast Committee., 1977 March 30; RG9.8-174; Format: Reel TRT: 29:30 (Box 55, Folder 174)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr., Cathy Goldman, and James Hill discuss reasons why only fifteen percent of children eligible for free breakfast through the Child Nutrition Act are receiving it.
    - Robinson, David -- representative from United Harlem Growth, Inc., 1977 March 30; RG9.8-160; Format: Reel TRT: 29:30 (Box 53, Folder 160)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and David Robinson discuss non-profit organizations that are actively reconstructing homes in the inner-city, including United Harlem Growth, Inc.
    - Barnes, Arthur -- President of the New York Urban Coalition., 1977 April 5; RG9.8-113; Format: Reel TRT: 29;30 (Box 50, Folder 113)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Arthur Barnes discuss the future of New York City and how the New York Urban Coalition aims to continue helping minorities and the poor.
    - Perkins, Joseph -- Director of the Mid-Manhattan Branch of the NAACP's "Operation Rebound Project.", 1977 April 12; RG9.8-112; Format: Reel TRT: 29:30 (Box 50, Folder 112)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Joseph Perkins discuss the Mid-Manhattan branch of the NAACP's "Project Rebound," a federally-funded program aimed at finding employment for nearly 1200 ex-offenders.
    - Williams, Mary Lou and Peter O'Brien -- jazz pianist and producer., 1977 May 3; RG9.8-162; Format: Reel TRT: 29:30 (Box 53, Folder 162)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr., Mary Lou Williams, and Peter O'Brien discuss the significance of the upcoming concert Embraced, a show performed by Williams and Cecil Taylor at Carnegie Hall.
    - Montgomery, Barbara--actress from La MaMa Experimental Theatre Club's Macbeth., 1977 May 4; RG9.8-224; 1 sound tape reels; Format: 1/4 inch audio reel (Box 51, Folder 224)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and actress Barbara Montgomery discuss La MaMa's Macbeth production.
    - Stewart, Ellen -- La MaMa Experimental Theatre Club., 1977 May 10; RG9.8-58; Format: Reel TRT: 29:30 (Box 52, Folder 58)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Ellen Stewart discuss international theatre, including La MaMa's decision to begin touring Europe in 1965 when critics were not reviewing their shows.
    - Carr, Ivory -- Director of the Outpatient Department at the Jewish Hospital and Medical Center of Brooklyn., 1977 May 21; RG9.8-75; Format: Reel TRT: 29:30 (Box 41, Folder 75)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Ivory Carr discuss how outpatient medical care for many New Yorkers may be threatened by proposed cutbacks in the Ghetto Medicine Program.
    - Killens, John O. -- author of The Resurrection of Alexander Pushkin., 1977 June 1; RG9.8-177; Format: Reel TRT: 29:30 (Box 55, Folder 177)
      Scope and Edits
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and John O. Killens discuss Killens' new book The Resurrection of Alexander Puskin, which aims to recognize Puskin in America at a time when he was more well-known in the Soviet Union because he was not freely translated into English.
    - Stewart, Ruth Ann -- Assistant Curator for the Schomburg Center for Research in Black Culture of the New York Public Library., 1977 June 15; RG9.8-111; Format: Reel TRT: 29:30 (Box 50, Folder 111)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Ruth Ann Stewart discuss the history and collection of the New York Public Library's Schomburg Center for Research in Black Culture in Harlem. They also discuss funding for a new facility since outgrowing its 135th Street location.
    - Roberts, Lillian -- Associate Director of District Council #37., 1977 July 20; RG9.8-178; Format: Reel TRT: 29:30 (Box 55, Folder 178)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Lillian Roberts discuss unemployment in the Black community.
    - Rowe, Billy and John Procope -- a distinguished journalist, and the publisher of NY Amsterdam News., 1977 June 21; RG9.8-57; Format: Reel TRT: 29:30 (Box 52, Folder 57)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr., Billy Rowe, and John Procope discuss the 150th Anniversary of the founding of the Black press, which began with Samuel Cornish's and John B. Russwurm's newspaper Freedom's Journal.
    - Ford, Connie -- Executive Director of the Police Athletic League., 1977 June 22; RG9.8-110; Format: Reel TRT: 29:00 (Box 50, Folder 110)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Connie Ford discuss some of the common activities of the Police Athletic League (PAL), which serves nearly 60,000 New York City boys and girls during the winter and summer months. Their discussion occurs shortly after the Criminal Justice Control Commission provides funding for their YES I CAN (Youth Enrichment Services Through Cooperation and Achievement) program aimed at pre-delinquent boys and girls.
    - Jones, Duane -- Executive Director of the Black Theatre Alliance., 1977 July 5; RG9.8-109; Format: Reel TRT: 29:30 (Box 50, Folder 109)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Duane Jones of the Black Theatre Alliance, a coalition of Black theatre and dance groups, discuss new developments in Black theatre and dance at a time when both are growing in importance within the greater theatre and dance community.
    - Barron, Allan -- Editor and Publisher of Black Sports Magazine., 1977 July 20; RG9.8-56; Format: Reel TRT: 29:30 (Box 52, Folder 56)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr. and Allan Barron discuss some of the persisting, negative racial attitudes in sports despite the growing number of successful Black athletes.
    - Rhoden, John, Romare Bearden, and Larry Wilson -- a sculptor, an artist, and a representative from Philip Morris, Inc., 1977 July 28; RG9.8-132; Format: Reel TRT: 29:30 (Box 50, Folder 132)
      Dr. Roscoe C. Brown, Jr., artists Romare Bearden and John Roden, and sponsor Larry Wilson discuss the Brooklyn Museum of Art's exhibition Two Centuries of Black American Art.